http://www.eeri.org/privacy-policy

Earthquake Engineering Research InstituteEERI - an international, technical society of engineers, geoscientists, architects, planners, public officials, & social scientists
Login Here
Home
About EERI
Our Mission
Board of Directors
Laurie A. Johnson
David Cocke
Lucy Arendt
Learning from Earthquakes
School Earthquake Safety Initiative (SESI)
Housner Fellows Program
Housner Fellows Program
2020 Housner Fellows
2017 Housner Fellows
2014 Housner Fellows
2012 Housner Fellows
Housner Blog
Friedman Family Visiting Professionals Program
Public Policy
What is Public Policy?
Legislative Action Center
Policy Statements
Implementing an Effective Earthquake Early Warning System
Promoting the Use of Confined Masonry Construction
Creating Earthquake-Resilient Communities
Schools shall be URM Free by 2033
Mitigation of Nonstructural Hazards in Schools
National Earthquake Hazards Reduction Program
Data Collection
Earthquake Engineering Research Institute collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. Examples of this type of data are: the name of your Internet service provider, the site that referred you to us, any pages you request, and the time and date of those requests, etc. There are instances where Earthquake Engineering Research Institute requests personally identifiable information to provide site visitors with a service. This information, such as name, mailing address, email address, and type of request, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the request, as determined by Earthquake Engineering Research Institute, to fulfill your needs.
Information Sharing
Personally identifiable Information collected on our website is never provided or sold to any other company for that company’s independent use without your consent.
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.
We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
Cookies
Earthquake Engineering Research Institute may send your browser a “cookie” that uniquely identifies your browser. Your browser will store the cookie as a string of characters that will be sent back to our website to improve the user experience of our website. Many websites will not work without the use of cookies. It is possible to set your browser to reject cookies, but be aware that some web services or features of our site may not function properly.
Links
Our site may link to other sites, which are outside of our domain. When you follow a link from our site, we advise you to check the privacy statements of those external sites before providing any personally identifiable information.
Latest News
EERI names new co-chairs of Learning from Earthquakes CommitteeA message from the EERI President, Laurie A. JohnsonWebinar: Earthquakes in Pandemics – Experiences from Earthquakes in EuropeEERI Releases Earthquake Spectra Special Issue on GEM’s 2018 Global Hazard and Risk ModelsWebinar: Citizen Advocacy — Tools to Advance Seismic Safety PolicyWebinar Series: Applying Lessons Learned from COVID-19 to Earthquake Preparedness2021 EERI Annual Meeting: Call for Session Proposals
Our Subscribing Members
Visionary & Platinum members
Gold members
Silver members
Bronze members
Follow us
Become a Member
At every stage of your career, we provide you with the resources and connections you need to succeed and make an impact. Join EERI today!
Earthquake Engineering Research Institute | 499 14th Street, Suite 220 | Oakland, CA 94612
phone: 510-451-0905 | fax: 510-451-5411 | eeri@eeri.org
Terms
and
Privacy Policy
